L: hello?
V: hello everybody welcome it's me it's Vox
V: it's the boys from Luxiem
V: how are we all doing we're here today
V: in the depths of the jungle
V: from the home of the monkeys of Luxiem
V: ready to have a lovely relaxed um
V: uh
V: discussion on how we felt about our first month
V: it's gonna be intimate
V: it's gonna be fun
V: and most of all
V: it's gonna involve boys
V: so to start with, why don't in debut...
V: why don't in debut order
V: why don't we introduce ourselves
V: let's start with... Luca!
L: oh me? oh
L: hi hi okay
L: are you getting ready for this today?
S: yeah
L: hi everyone
L: pog you
L: I'm Luca
S: pooog you
L: it's uh... it's honest it's like 4am for me right now
L: so sorry if I don't sound like very energetic at all
L: but uh yeah I'm uh... Luca Kaneshiro from NIJISANJI's Luxiem
L: it's very nice to meet you
L: very nice to see you
V: let's goooo
S: let's goooo
V: thank you Luca
V: now
V: Shu!
S: you sound like 4p... oh
V: oh shit sorry
S: *laugh*
S: oh Shu!
S: uh Shu! Ya... Yamino!
S: oooh Shu! Yeah! ooooh ooooh
S: you know there's fire in the background of the thumbnail
S: but I don't have any fire right now but
V: Luca there's fire in your face right now
V: scream
S: everybody subscribe
V: everybody subscribe to Shu right fucking now
S: wait but you're on Vox's channel right now
V: you subscribe to both that we're both pretty cool
S: oh yeah yeah yeah
S: all right and after me is... Eveland
V: Mysta, Mys...
I: Eveland? I have a full name
V: ***
I: yeah hi everyone, I'm Ike Eveland
I: a virtual novelist from NIJISANJI EN's Luxiem
I: it's nice to see you all here and oh my god
I: zhow has it already been a month
V: it's crazy right?
S: oh Vox you're alerts
V: my legs they're behind... *gasp* you're behind the table
S: in the jungle, the mighty jungle
V: Mysta please
I: and now for the birthday child
V: the birthday boy
M: uh...
L: sussy boy
M: hello everyone I'm Mysta Rias
M: apparently it's my birthday today but don't tell anyone okay
M: okay
S: hey sussie boy
M: god that wasn't really ***
L: you had a good birthday today though?
M: yeah it was good
L: is it pog?
M: community made some really nice videos and I watched it
S: I saw I saw
M: that's really cute
S: eyyyyyyy
L: it's fun!
M: sorry for a little quiet
M: uh I'm still kind of drunk and I'm also really out of energy, chat
M: so, eyyyy
S: hmm
V: and thank you Mysta. and last of all, I'm Vox
S: oh wait
S: hi Vox
V: hiiiiii
I: just just that?
V: that's... I'm Vox
S: hello Vox
V: I'm a 400 year old fucking granddad and my knees hurt
V: welcome to Luxiem
S: well welcome
V: welcome!
???: thank you
V: so...
S: I'm welcoming you, you, you, and you in chat
M: me?
S: oh in chat
V: really?
M: oh
V: if when we say you in chat we're talking about you
V: you right now you're listening
L: yeah I'm looking at you
M: yep yeah get that hand away from there
V: lux baby go
I: specifically
M: ***
I: I just think I have a random name
L: me? me?
S: oh I can pick your nose I can pick your nose
L: wait what the hell
V: let's go!
S: oh gotten Luca's nose
L: oh!
S: I can pick Luca's nose
V: get the buggers out! get them out!
S: I could like touch Vox's back after that
V: oh yeah scratch my back, scratch my back please
V: can you scratch my back yeah
S: bugger scratch bugger scratch
V: oh thank you thank you
M: don't touch us
L: ***
L: how was that how was this month been for all of you
L: has it been...
S: oh it has been a month
M: of course it's been a month it's our one month anniversary stream
M: what are you guys on about
M: I'm the drunk one here what...
M: it has been one month
S: it's it's like...
I: I don't think that's what he asked
V: it's been a long time ago
M: wait, am I
S: ***
S: but but it's a month, but it's... it's a...
S: it's a... what do you call it? it was... it was a short time
V: it felt short suddenly
L: ***
S: it felt short yeah that's the word, that's word
M: yeah
I: it feels short like at this moment
I: it feels like it's just flown by
I: but after the first week, I just kind of felt like we've been here forever
M: yeah
V: yeah
M: that's weird
I: it's strange how that kind of changes as time goes on
S: you feel like we've known each other for like... forever
L: oh like we've known them for like three months already
L: it was it was actually
S: well I mean it's kind of accurate
M: that's pretty accurate yeah
V: it's a while
M: you know I still have um... I still have the first picture that we took together
V: really
M: I *** each other in video call
V: yeah
I: oh yeah I remember that
V: the big group selfie
M: I can send it immediately chat
M: I can send it
S: oh that one
V: if you tweet that people are going to go wild yeah
M: oh yeah I can do it
I: do it do it do it do it
M: I need to find it ,it's probably hidden somewhere on the files but...
S: pog champion
M: I remember that day
L: wait tweet what?
M:  that were...
S: ***
M:  we were also happy
V: thank you guys so much for the SUPAs
S: thank you thank you thank you thank you!
V: thank you for the SUPAs!
V: supporting us around one month
S: there are... the one month special it's free on Vox's stream
S: pog pog pog pog pog
S: pog
V: it's one month special it's all
I: it appears that I have frozen
V: oh no Ike
V: Ike your stasis no
S: in to the unknown~
V: ***
L: ***
S: in to the unknown~
you know one of the side effects I believe of um... of traveling through time is that
sometimes you'll operate on a different frame rate uh to the rest of... to the rest of people
I even think it's the frame rate because like my hair and stuff is moving it's just me
there's a bit of lag you know
you're you're sort of your server is in the past and you're sort of um
your servers the expat is in is in present day so
uh-huh
oh my bit rate has gone to zero um that's a show oh
yeah oh the stream first
oh my god no I was worried about this
wait no wait i think it's going back up okay we're fine we're
***
i think so
youtube what is flick calling it's like flickering on and off
what's happening I don't understand I think
why now are we are we
let's just give it just be patient should be patient
the bitrate is hovering
you know I keep having this
I have this experience on stream quite often where
like I don't know why it just happens to me quite
uh like at least once or twice a stream that my bit rate will just plummet for a few minutes
and then it will come back yeah
um but every time it happens I'll see someone put the buffering emoji in chat
and what it means is is that at any time someone could put the buffering emoji in and instantly
I will see it I'll be like and then I will just I'll just take a look at it
and then immediately I'll check my bitrate and be like shit shit no not now not now
and then they could just be fuckin' with me
yeah
or it's just like somebody individual that's just like my internet's going to crap
it must be the fault of the someone who's like thinking
they're just like hmm
I can't process this
before the great crash
me stuttering about
we were talking about
oh yeah yeah it's like it's a month
it's been a long time
Ike is I like uh
I don't like because I never traveled through time I'm just old
uh so I'm still on my original server you know
we've got that zero ping ethernet connection
five thousand years old now uh Vox
how old are you again
I'm I'm I'm I'm a ripe 400 and something you know
memory's hazy but we're getting there
400 something
400 something never felt so young and more my life
wow seems good enough
rumor
oh you beat me to it this shut the fuck up
shut the fuck up
i mean
spongebob you're never gonna live uh live up to this if you don't get this thing off your chest
I'm old and I'm proud I'm a boomer and I'm proud
what's the actual like age range for a boomer
i think it's like 40 something
oh no that's that's like old and then some
hang on
how old is a boomer
they're between 58 and 67.
anyone born between 1955 and 1964.
oh oh
then Vox is not a boomer
so it's anyone from from the age 58 to 76 is a boomer
box isn't that a boomerang
isn't that around like
i never traveled I'd probably be I'd be a boomer by now
yeah Luca would be a boomer
a boomer
boomer
Lucas boomer all of us traveling
hang on
let me wait let me have a look
so apparently based on my birthday I'd be a
I'm I'm I'm not a boomer I'm a puritan
the generation from from 1588 to 1617 was the puritan generation
uh under the rule of um
john winthrop and anne hutchinson
so I mean if I was if I was if I was born in in england I believe then yes
oh yes but you're under the rule of your your own right
yeah yeah so I can just pick my pick myself up
I'm from I'm from I'm from the I'm from the uh
from the myself
I'm from the myself I'm from the I'm from the Vox generation you know
we just we oh yeah
me and the boys
oh why did I use this ugly green senpai this time around
I don't know if you guys saw the shenanigans that went down
you mean the you mean the chan
chan
i mean you can call me that that's fine
you've allowed us and now you will suffer the consequences like
you're my wave mates your you guys are allowed to call me nicknames
and I can't remember when when that senpai is calling me things
I don't really have to say
they're semifinals
i call
i call I i called you my love the other day
and then you called me family
like a big family aren't we
we are like a big family aren't we
yeah
you guys are my brothers
yeah apparently
you've so like volume wise
and according to chad I see some people oh oh
i did just turn you up on discord let me try turning up a little bit more
hmm
sauce michael here
sauce
earned you all we all
so you see this image of Riku Tazumi
where are your fingers
to answer this question we have to go back to 1967
when mysterious was but was was was but a wee babe
huh
he's still a wee babe
you call me babe
is his keen sense of smell
really
akin to a dog
unless
you're pregnant
you smell
mr
he smells the future of the clan
the future the future of the clan
he knows oh he's sniffing right now
he knows
I'm lost that was me that was me sniffing
oh
oh you're a sniffer I'm obsessed with that video
you know the one of the person who has the little microphone
and they go up to the dog and they're like can I get a few words
and the dog just goes
i love those videos
that was a pretty good impression
yeah that was yeah
i like that everyone likes the one of the seal
who goes like eggs
it kind of sounds like me and mahjong
if you start getting sweaty
like really into it I think it is up there
maybe maybe I should learn how to play
no how do you if you if you ever go crazy with poker
and if you're like oh this is a full house
you know they're kind of vibe
I've never played poker in my life oh
okay
maybe that was a bad comparison
oh what else do you play blackjack for what it's worth
oh
i guess it's like oh I have a I love that
the moment we mentioned
oh my gosh the poker legend
I learned a lot about the casino
we need you to do a stream of the mario 64 ds minigames with luigi in the
baby
pretty casino that according to new laws
like that section of the game has to be rated 18 which is so funny
the gambling
yeah yeah because of gambling like luigi dealing
oh like
because of that and of course I was like I was front and center for that you know
that's so crazy
i remember
i remember betting five coins every time
yes i was in there
all in
oh yeah Ike I'm I'm trying to turn you up
but I think it might be your compressor
like every time I turn you up you stay the same volume on discord
really ha wait hang on hang on
no no I fixed it I fixed it never mind
I i just realized that I i had been turning Shus volume up the entire time
you hear me
now I'm I i tricked it I turned you down just in time
like the litmus test to find out if someone is actually me
you smell you smell good
yay
every single member every member of Luxiem smells excellent
okay that brings up an interesting question
like if each of us had like an official like cologne what kind of scent would it be
oh I've actually oh you know
yeah there was there was somebody who actually actually put one oh my god
you're right oh my god I'm an idiot
let's see can I dig that tweet up
you're going to do it
you're like you want to know why I like chat
I smell like um lynx tobacco and amber
it's what I i spray on myself why
why is that kind like like I feel like i should be disgusted but that sounds kind of sexy actually
it's really nice it's like a smoky type of smell um
smokey
that's not just your kitchen
the instant you mentioned body spray mister I just had like the mental image of
I don't know why because there are all the comparisons to you being a dog
i just saw just you biting down on a butt kind of deodorant fucking blowing up
someone needs to draw that
i remember when I was younger and I had a really dumb moment
where I found like a really rusty like spray can lying around
so I threw a rock at it with a friend until it like ruptured so it started spraying out
and then I was dumb enough to like I wonder what happened if I point this towards my hair
oh
i mean um i had blue hair for a while
oh sure
i mean more blue than it already is
i see the residues still there like it's still there
no that's natural I was talking like about like in the middle of everything
like like imagine like at the very top of my head like it's just a big blue dot
or are you sure it's blue i think it just like creeped down as your hair grew I think it's still there
maybe it got absorbed into my dna and just kind of went out to the tips
yeah your future generation your child will have like blue hair
yeah all thanks to a ruptured spray can
everyone keeps talking about lag in chat my bitrate is fine it's either youtube or you please
don't make don't make me worry again
yeah I'm watching the stream live so if anything happens then
then mister's gonna tune in and he's like yo you're fucked
no there's been like stutters but it lasts like point five seconds and then it comes yeah no way
you guys you guys you just you're just gonna have to cope I'm afraid
mold
that dream is
reminded me when I was a kid
um some kid for a rock at my head and i left a dent
oh my god
there's a dent
well not anymore oh
actually
i didn't want to tell on them because they were they went up to me
and they were like oh all right don't tell your mum
I was like are we just talking about head injuries
uh-huh
okay head injuries
why are you laughing
I was just because of luke luke has like been relatively tuned out for a bit
and she's like you guys talking about head injury
okay that is kind of funny
I'd like to imagine that was how that was how Luca made connections like in the mafia
he would just go up to like the the leader of an opposing family
just sit down at the table at about an exclusive club and be like
hey you guys talking about head injuries
i mean that is one way my son died of a concussion the other week
why are you talking to me like this young man what's wrong with you
i was saying like I i uh
i also hurt my head when I was
oh
when I was younger
oh no
i don't all right did you want to hear
it yeah yeah yeah
it's all dumb
so I i was i was dipping my head on a bucket
a bucket full of water
and i didn't realize that there was a tap on top of it
i was
it was not good
would you guys believe me if I said that i also had a really bad head injury
oh really
i think I've told this story on stream once but um
i was really into doing parkour when i was younger
and there was this one time when I was gonna like like jump over a wall of sorts
and my feet like got stuck on the edge and kind of hooked in
and because they got hooked in it essentially swung me like face first
and then when I slammed into the wall my feet disconnected
and I fell head first into the curve
i had a pretty bad um experience with that as well
um I remember I remember you two
yeah a couple decades ago um some friends and I we were um
I think it was quite late and we all we all went out and we
you know how you know how when you're drunk and then and it's like quite late and you find like a park you know
and suddenly you get the urge to be like oh let's go let's go let's go fuck around on like the play equipment and stuff
you know zip zip like zip lines
like the ones where it's like you know it has the long thing that hangs off with the seat on the bottom
i hopped on and I was like somebody somebody revved me up some somebody gave me some speed you know
somebody fucking power me on and they were like how fast you want to go
and I was like really fast they're like really sure and I was like yeah yeah fucking fucking you know
and they and I underestimate i underestimated how strong my friend was
he fucking arnold schwarzenegger just powered me along
and was like I'll see you on the other side
and i hit hit the opposite end of the zip wire
and I swear to god it hung down I went up by a hundred and eighty degrees
and was about 30 feet like 30 meters in the sky
and in that moment I was like that's it I'm dead
and then it just it went up to the top fell straight down and right as it was about to swing away
i hung on right until it was close to the ground and then I let go
and it just my head just kind of like bounced off the ground
it was really fucking nasty
i know I shouldn't be I'm so sorry for laughing
but the way that you're describing it with the sound effects is genuinely hilarious
it was a big event it was a story transpiring you know i almost died
oh my gosh no
the akuma clan would have ended there
that's it that would have been the legacy over with its last its last ruling member just just wiped out by a zip line
you're the only one left without head trauma come on
it's like the k rule trailer where there's just the k rule shaped hole in the ground
i don't have a head injury but
oh what do I have
maybe that's why you're the brightest out of all of us
every single member of luxian butt Shu has like yeah
oh but um oh I do have an injury
oh when I was like i was like how old was I
i was it infant it was like right after
you know all the I mean obviously the poop like hitting me and getting into the fire was a pretty big injury
but like after that I was I was also like still learning how to walk
and then i was walking and then
apparently I don't know any of this because like I was too young for it
but like apparently I stabbed my head against like a corner of a table
oh god and
when I look at my forehead there's like a really small scar
so i think it's it's
i assume it's behind your bangs
yeah it's like really high up it's really high up on the
table corner injury is a very ipad kid injury to receive you know what I mean
i that happened to me yesterday okay
i was just wait yesterday
I was holding my food and my thigh actually slammed onto the side of the other corner of the table
oh you got something now
it was fine
that's all that matters
do you swear like you stub your toe on
oh yeah
yeah I go at it
oh yeah you do
shut up besides the table is too sharp
a lot of times you just go like how could this happen to me
hello darkness my old friend
yeah usually I don't swear I didn't get caught very striked again
a lot of time I don't I don't swear but I'm just like
oh yes this has to happen to me again yes okay okay
and then i just like you go into full sarcasm mode
yeah usually I'm like all right here we go again
the collab is off go home everybody
shit
all right bye guys
i actually have something I actually have some chronic some clotted cream fudge here that I got for christmas
there's a little bit there's only a little bit left
yes clotted cream mister
what is that
they'll actually know what if that likes cream
no
it's cream but something else is done too
thick creamy by heating full cream cow's milk using steam or a water bath
and then leaving it in shallow pans to cool slowly
how do you use steam to heat something
oh my fucking god
isn't steam made from heating something not the other way around
it's made from heating water yes
and then you use the steam which has heat to heat something else
how do you know the milk the next time you boil water
the milk
i mean how do you not get the milk with water
i mean mister you know that like like something that's hot has the possibility to transfer that heat to something else
like have you never been in a sauna and thrown water on
uh hot rocks I've been in a sauna before yeah
yeah when you throw water on the hot rocks everything gets so much like hotter when you're higher up
and that's because of the steam
oh i was really like just observing myself when I was younger
what did they have a mirror in there or something
more important more important more important very very
okay
I was just looking at my body
yeah
you gotta you gotta make sure you don't overheat yourself too yeah
I hate that
have you all been in a sauna before yeah
man yeah yeah
oh I've yeah
I've never been in a sauna
to be fair I think with those tattoos in that body I feel like the attention luke would get in a sauna would be like
you know impossible to deal with
I know right I'd be touching them
yeah me too
oh I feel like I feel like you could just go to like
your mafia's privately owned sauna yeah
privately owned owned uh facilities with your with your uh your members
I'm willing to admit that there's a kind of uh onsen somewhere
I'd love to believe that he he goes in like that and
not anymore I'm rebuilding it okay
okay
his bodyguards are outside and then at one point he's like hey yo tony come in here
put put some of this lotion on my back i wanna I wanna I wanna feel clean
put some of this fucking lotion on my back
and he's like all right boss yes I'll do what you do what you ask my boy
I can't boss I can't like like like Luca's australian but I can't think of any accent for a mafia man that is not like italian-american
fedora
I'm working here
on the topic of saunas has anybody ever been in a sauna that's like really hot I'm talking like a hundred degrees plus celsius
and then immediately when they go outside they jump into like an ice lake
oh
no but to be fair like you are swedish
so that that kind of that kind of that kind of fits you know
I feel like you guys are more accustomed to the cold
oh I found the the colognes
oh you did
yeah the hell is the gucci guilty a
gucci what
gucci is the brand
and guilty is the they make alone
oh so is this like colognes that we would wear
yeah yeah yeah
oh okay I thought they like made mods like like like made-up ones based off of us
that's that's pretty gucci
oh my gosh is this named fabulous
oh tom ford oh very nice
um joe malone would sage and sea salt
I'm alone
I'm going to read it
wait wait wait
malone dick in your mouth
mo
laughing at the punch line for once Luca
mr said it before me
that took me
I'm so excited though
like now that we're um
you know I don't know what your guys situations were like before um we became part of this lovely organization
but I mean I don't know so then I'll be I'll actually be able to afford fragrances like this
this this is exciting
maybe maybe in celebration I might buy like some tom ford
um a 50 milliliter bottle of fucking fabulous is 240 pounds
it's quite expensive
it's gonna smell good it's gotta smell good
you roll up to the club wearing that you know you're walking home with uh some self-respect
hmm
i have like so much cologne that I've like acquired over the years
because I'm like I i get that like urge sometimes
like you know what I want to be a little bit fancy
and then I use it like maybe once or twice
and then I just forget about it and now I have like eight of them just standing around
oh my god
guilt gucci guilty's a kind of gucci
oh yeah gucci's like
expensive right
it's very expensive yeah
a 50 milliliter one's like 175 au so
one 130
us baby
how much are you spending per milliliter
father son and house of gucci
oh my oh my what
god gucci looks weird
it does sound like you're saying coochie
son and house of coochie
never mind oh no
after a month some things never change
i feel like this will never change
yeah
a year of whatever a decade
guys remember when we um when we first like started hanging out
um and we um we all did the rice purity test
and it was
you know what
oh you you told them
yeah i
yeah
I don't think it's that big a deal
because it doesn't show what he's fighting for you because you know
you know
I've only mentioned that there's a wide
range wait did you tell them all of ours or just your own
no no it's just mine oh
okay okay okay
why is this a secret it's like it's like a random little quiz on the internet
yeah I know I so I think it's that there's there's no way
i mean if you're if you're willing to share it you know
spill
the motherfuc-
i mean I mean I don't mind sharing my score
yeah I'm not sure yours is pure
where is it where is it
i even remember I feel like I feel like i feel like I should do it again because i can't remember what I got last time
do we not have it like saved and like
yeah it should it should be saved in like
yeah it's black yeah I think yeah
it probably is
you can search um through messages oh it's so sweet though
the first question on it is have you held hands romantically
I'm like yeah as it goes like down yeah
people shy
oh god the the last question on it oh I don't know if I could even say that
yeah
yeah I don't think it's allowed
wait what's my score
files
control f
I'm scrolling through the the group chat right now
and this is so such nostalgia for me at this point
yeah like when we first kind of started talking oh
yeah yeah
the first message in the entire thing
oh never mind it's not the first message never mind I thought it was for a second
i thought it was linking a swamp meme
is it wait wait is it is it the one which is
oh wait do we want to like just like search through like our our like earliest interactions and slack
honestly let's do it
hey what
and then jump to the very beginning oh
wait you can do that
yeah
it's a nation what did you get that intonation I just did
wait you can do that
oh my gosh
it was so much lower than I thought
holy
there it is I am
i am
96.
oh what
what oh
is there something wrong with this
no no no there's nothing wrong with it
I'm just impressed
he's he's really been he's really gotten around hasn't he
yeah
wait wait yeah what does that even do that's higher than the tide on me
like rice purity is like more of what you do not what you know so
yeah it's fair
exactly
which can be seen or a bad thing i suppose depending on which end you're on
oh yeah definitely definitely
mrs probably the negatives
i mean
no
what else is in this place
i don't even remember what's on that list
I mean at some point it gets really absurd
yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
oh god my first message is oh hello i just woke up lmao 5 16 pm
wait shoot shoot I've been I've been reading through the messages did you share what your score was
yeah a little bit literally just said it
right okay I was zoned out I'm sorry
yeah it was uh november 13th
one of my first messages in this is the outtakes I have for hope and the dog
and I was this close to being like
i wonder what that is I'm just clicking play and of course I have desktop audio on so it would have just everyone fine
if you play it
go right ahead
let's do it everybody these are ike's outtakes
wow
lyrics is a good thing to remember
it was so cute like I love you
I love
these I i like on the last one you just hear like
that's like a brain fart in real time because you hear me
no no no and like after that like you can hear me it sounds like I'm going quiet but you if you listen closely you can hear me
like my brain is desperately trying to get the syllables out and it's just not happening
i just seen a message from shu
saying i urinated in the forest once
yeah public urination
let's go
why is that statement on its own in a vacuum so funny
oh my god that's how one of my points went away
nostalge
this is like one of the first convos we had and I said I'm so sweaty I need a bath
Ike called me I said get clean boy and Luca said bath pog
nothing has changed over
nothing actually nothing is just that
i wonder if there's anything that happened
in a bathtub
oh when I started compiling stuff in evidence.
oh yeah evidence.zip
have you ever actually used that
I used
oh like when I started taking screen caps of oh I didn't use this one
which one
no
not that one there's
jesus christ
I think actually I think elira's empire might have tweeted that
like I think somebody tweeted it
wait which which one are you talking about
I'm I'm again I'm just looking at put it in there
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
mister oh my god that's a joke his rice purity is not two
that would be really bad
it's not me
nobody should be tattooed yeah
if mine was two then I'd be arrested
actually
that is true yeah what the hell
I mean i i still I still stand by the fact that i think that chart is a massive missed opportunity
no I am not naming my r tag short
no
wait can you show the screenshot or like
i think I think they need to see this
yeah the screenshot itself is so much funnier
oh my god
you can't do that
no that that right there that's just luxian plus oliver
actually I'm just gonna I'm just gonna what is
it the meme that Luca just said
you cannot put that on
you actually cannot I forbid it
who who was it that made
that chat
for those who know the old five in the back one in front you know what I mean
one in the front
people don't know why
why did I make that
I don't know why did you make this
that's a good question
we
I'm trying to remember can we find
it is it in random or is it a worry chat wait hold on
it's back it's back
it's back chat don't worry oh
oh I i know why I made it now
you're like I'm 173 with with no heels
i just I just put that together
it made you really tiny
i don't know about you but this picture doesn't really exude that it's about like you know height
i don't think that's the subject matter of this
oh no I'm I don't know why I'm thinking about
the the way that you're edited into this meme you look slightly wider than normal
I'm just thinking about it
what was that what was that video I made of you the man of sex
where he just emerged from jail
you made what
do you remember that it's this it's this screenshot from tf2 where there's an outline if somebody threw a wind through like a wall or something
and their name just says the man of sex and it plays a song that's like
yeah I do I do vaguely remember that
wrong use of the meme
people who've been keeping up with lux and laura gonna get all of these
it's gonna be great
I'm like oh I was there for that tweet
i rem I remember there will be like leonardo dicaprio pointing on the couch
one second
it's insanity I mean
I'm trying to find the old tweets that we did um like right before debut you know
and like going back it's like yeah
I've made 750 tweets since then I'm like damn it's only been a month what the fuck
it really is
more than me
789 okay but that has to be a lot of retweets
yeah
I'll like check a lot of money right my retweets as well
how do you check
is it on the mobile
i think I think it is a mobile
mobile
how many tweets have I made
how many tweets of luxia made
how do I check how many tweets I made
yeah you go into uh you going to mobile
i just thought of something
we all talked about how like certain things haven't changed
since like prior to prior to debut
but what about what are some things that have changed for you guys
um
wait repeat the question sir I was uh i was not on my
like what's something that a lot of things have like stayed relatively the same ever since we first started like hanging out and since we debuted
but what are some things that like have changed like preferably something positive
uh I think I've talked to more people
hmm
how many collabs I did today and I think i did 16 since debut which is quite a lot damn
that is a lot isn't it yeah
and that's only on my channel
that's pretty sure
i don't even know how many I've done
i remember in my second week like once we were um once it sort of opened up and we were
and we could collab with everybody like i would collab with so many people like i was just so excited
oh this is my boy piss
hang on
one thing that changed
i spoke more japanese
that makes two of us nice
yeah
i don't think I've spoken this much japanese and I don't know how long
it's it's I'm I'm very very much not used to it
one thing that has um
i guess I'm pogging more definitely
you know Shu pocket
you mean to tell me that you haven't haven't always been pogging as much as you are now
that's just what Luca does
yeah I I've been if I was pogging times 10 before debut I'm plugging times 1000 now
whoa hundred times more
pog
right hundred times
i can't really like say anything that's if
nothing's really like change change for me but it's it's uh you know it's been very
it's been very happy
didn't you say you stopped watching anime
yeah I stopped watching it yeah I've had no time for anime anymore
don't know
I've had a little bit of time to watch anime thankfully I'm very thankful for that
but that's just me being a weeb
i probably would have time
but I just decided not to
I've had a lot of time for comfort youtubers
I don't I don't want that much anime
I watch oh yeah I watch linus tech tips
that's my comfort watch I just like listening to this little canadian man be like this is a computer with 19 cuda cores
and like I don't know what the fuck those are but keep talking your magic to me little man
i watched the the lock picking lawyer
the long picking lawyer what
oh yeah he's good disney
there's a guy that just has a whole collection of locks and he just picks locks
and like this lock has two serrated pins one one very long pin that's not like the other pins
and you you could pick them by using a tension wrench and the the pins that's included in the kit that i sell online over at covert instruments.com
yeah
that's what they say
a comfort youtuber that I like is a game review channel
that covers basically sort of any sort of games
but like the way he covers them like from stories from the history development history
and also it's very very in-depth very detailed and he's
the way the presentation is hilarious at times and also just really relaxing at times
i find myself falling asleep to it it's a channel called some call me johnny
and I just really really adore it and I feel like more people should appreciate
it it's like really really underrated in my opinion
also welcome back
hi hi
welcome back mister hello
we're talking about comfort watches on youtube
oh mr beast
mysteries
this guy this guy opened his wallet and mysterious popped out
this guy oh
mystery has popped out
it just popped i don't know where that came from from the darkest like part of my head
I don't know why I said that but something about just someone opening his wall and being like all right time to get my credit card up ms is like yeah
and then mister would be like scared of the dark be like no I don't want to be in here anymore
let me out
i didn't wash my hands chat no
and he's gonna use it yeah jerk me off
rice purity minus one
minus one oh that is one
is there gonna be a rice purity score for just like you have never washed your hands
i wouldn't want to
i remember seeing like this video covering a dude
I don't know where he was from but he like hasn't had a bath in like 13 years or something ah
what that's kind of pug champ
i mean at that point you're just gonna admire the dedication
imagine the stench
yeah
imagine the smell
of thinking it
who's gonna be the one to say it
imagine the taste
wait wait wait wait
is that what you were talking about no
i was thinking about the you smell thing
why did you go to jail
you didn't even get that
oh
I was just staring at the poop on the table
this probably smells a bit as it sits here
I'm quite pungent indeed
oh no
no don't
how does it feel to have your arch nemesis just chilling on the table like that
i mean it's poop
that it is damn he really really did be spitting facts
the poop itself was not at fault in the end it was the guy that controlled the poop
um are we ever gonna get lore of you going back in time to just kind of fuck that guy up you know
i don't know I kind of like this time era
okay fair enough
so very like the villain but he's sort of just helped come back easy
you know I've watched my fair share of steins gay I'm scared of the butterfly effect
one small act can change drastically you played until dawn how do you not know what the butterfly is yeah that's
what I know what it is
oh Luca asked who asked
oh my god
what the fuck what the hell
i mean there are times where some of us i can't really put my finger on who like that that I have a hard time discerning the voice
at least in the beginning i had a hard time
oh
you know that's me when mr impersonates ike
really
i i think I'm too too drunk to do this
oh no give it a try give it a try
mister
see the only reason why I could tell apart those two is because of the mic quality honestly
and then some people apparently when i like like uh yell and stuff I sound like Luca
really
oh yeah because both of you like yelling at boys don't you
first thing pog
head voice no
no
ah it's pretty close
I see it oh yeah
i can see it
usually usually it's like the oh no no pog pog
wait that was weird I thought that was Lucas saying that
yeah
i get I get yellow text over my subtitles
mm-hmm
the nintendo switch thing and like not very much oh yeah right
I'm so excited I'm so excited
uh the nintendo 64 games are added if you have the the newer online
um
nintendo online yeah yeah yeah yeah
expansion power whatever the heck yeah
yeah and then in there there's ah
i really want to play mario 64. I love that game so much
isn't that already available on like the the all-stars collection
um it is but the all-stars collection um was remo was mario was shot in the back of the head
on march 31st for march 31st mario was executed by reggie personally so yeah
now I would imagine it fetches for quite the hefty penny
yeah
i know shu has it and I'm jealous because you played married galaxy such a good game
I played it I played I 100 like earlier last year and oh my god oh I i miss i missed that game so much I wish I could play it through again
i mean it can but like I don't have mario all the stars
oh right yeah
I'm gonna when I get my when I get my ninja sanji paycheck I'm gonna buy a wii
yeah oh you should make a wii u 480p
let's go
if you buy a wii u you could connect it via hdmi
really
interesting yeah all right you can play wii games on a wii u can't you
yeah yeah
can you really
I want to get away with you just so I can play mystery dungeon
hmm I remember mentioning that yeah the wii controllers guys come on that's part of the experience
you know
like mario's hat and he spins my galaxy
that is mario galaxy yeah you're right
oh my god
um do you guys want to do the this all that questions that
that'd be fun yeah
no if you send me a link to that I'll I'll get that set up
yeah yeah here uh I'll put it again is
it sort of like that will you press the button like what the fuck did you just send
what did I why it's the gossip girl thing wait
oh yeah but mister said he was gonna go use the bathroom and I went to the one where it's just like
where's that girl I was so confused because i just said how do I look to how do I look today
and then I moused over it for one femtosecond and it just said I have to piss
and I was like i didn't even realize it was a gif
oh I didn't realize it was a gif either
me neither did i
go this girl
should we all open it is that a yeah
this or that questions
the first one is television series or movie
oh okay
who starts let's go one at a time
i I think um television series
yeah I watch anime
I'll go to the movie
i kind of sit down for the people as well
although I do love me my series but I'm I'm a movie person
we got three for tv two for movie
yeah I feel like I like series more than anime movies
yeah um
I mean if I'm going into a cinema then it's kind of different
but like just in general
I mean you wouldn't watch a tv series in a cinema
well yeah imagine experience though
that's gonna be him I have to be a very cinematically produced tv show
have you guys done uh used 3d like in a movie before because I've never done that
I'm
kind of oh yeah I have it's fantastic
i have it's ready
other times they just kind of convert a wait traditionally shot movie into 3d and it always looks bad
I remember once when I saw a movie that I i I won't name the movie itself
but I took my glasses off just to see like what the heck
because I didn't notice any 3d effect
and I i I'm not kidding you
the best 3d effect in the entire movie was the subtitles
yeah it's the text and everything you know because that literally like pops out all the time
oh sorry
oh I went to watch it like a 3d movie and then like you know in cinemas they have like all these like advertisements before the actual movie stars
like all the advertisements in the 3d theater were like amazing like they were so immersive
they were like like throwing things left and right on my face I was like oh oh wow
oh my gosh look at all these ass this mute this 3d movie must be amazing because of how the 3d technology is working and everything
and then the actual movie like the 3d is like so like flat I'm just like
okay the guy's nose is a little pointed out
you can see yeah I felt damn I feel like ebenezer scrooge's nose is about to just really brush my own nose damn
they they have actual 3d glasses now
though yeah they do the red blue ones yeah
yeah those have been gone for quite a while
wait yeah
the cinemas I've been to for like decades now
now if 3d was using those glasses which they probably do now
they have a lot better
yeah yeah
if you ever used to get like the thing where one of your eyes would just see one of the colors like after you take them off yeah
yeah yeah the red and blue
I always like i always used to feel dizzy like when i went to a cinema and saw and saw a movie in 3d and I'd leave
I just feel like like I just feel really dizzy I don't know why
i guess it's just the disconnect
someone in someone in chat just said 3d movies unpog scratch and sniff movies however
did you guys ever see what was it did you guys ever see spike kids four
yeah spikes oh my god
no I didn't I didn't but I saw the ads for I saw that there was literally
okay okay there is literally a moment in the film
where like a dog just takes a shit and then one of the like
the fact that like the way it works is they give you like that thing and there are numbers on it
and a number appears on screen it tells you which thing to scratch you can sniff it and smell what's in the film
and there's a moment where a dog just takes a shit and it's like number four and I'm like
it's it's a no from me it's a no from me
i remember when I was at I think it was universal studios
and I went to see shrek 4d
wait is that is that shrek forever after
no no no no like it's like a dedicated like short for like a ride
and there there's this one part I think it's donkey where donkey just sneezes at the screen
and there's like water water what is that that happens it's like sneezed in the face
the entire crowd just had like a collective groan of disgust when it happened
actually
yeah I went to a place in france a while ago called called futuroscope
and they had like simulators like that
and every time there was like oh it's like yeah no all you guys are going through the water
and then they would just spray a little war in your face just like I'm not having fun
hold on everybody I need it I i need a drink let me go I'm gonna quickly uh leave
uh don't encourage me to say the word band in my chat please
okay
let me just check the table
it kind of looks like uh august it kind of looks like augustus poop the poop
that's on on the top senpai
hello
what if we what if we do the what if we do the 180 and do something that's not banned
hmm
what is not banned
one band
unbanned
one three experience I remember that was actually good was also at universal
i remember it was like terminator 2 also a dedicated short for that attraction
and that was cool they had like a big room with three massive screens with projectors
and there was like actors actually running around on a stage
and on the projectors there were like cgi um like robots and whatnot
that actually reached out it was a really really cool show like that
when everything's created with the 3d in mind it can be really really cool
dang I know I I've never been to the theme park so
I'm gonna change that someday yes
we need it we need it
we need which one which one do you want to go
luxian theme park
I don't know anywhere anywhere that has the roller coaster
I've met never mind oh you've never ridden a roller coaster oh my gosh
and we're saying unbanned let's go
we're not banned anymore we can actually stream now let's go
let's go
i think I think we need to take you to like
a place that has like every world
disney world's roller coasters aren't as like is it freaking good
well no no it's it's it's friendlier I guess
I have emotions so I would
i never go on like
maybe the like the simulator rides will wouldn't be that well suited for mister then
really
yeah simulators can really get your motion sickness like pretty badly
ninja world
oh
six flags
I'm saying I need to go to bed I'm just drunk
it's fine it's only say seven o'clock for mister
yeah it's only 7 p.m guys
my eyes are just kind of not open because I'm I'm drunk I've been drinking
mister you and I have to go to spoons
oh yeah you want to spoon me
we gotta go i mean I mean I mean we can do we can always do both
we can do that at spoons
we can we can we can find one of the booths and just kind of sit in the back yeah
yeah I want to get a picture from the
hello darkness my old friend I want to go there
we can get a pic we can get a picture and then I'll get a picture of you
a picture of me drinking a picture
yeah
a picture
a picture of me drinking a picture
oh
yeah
oh clever boy
nina you're absolutely right
although i like that you like you like sex on the beach don't you
I mean I mean you're involved I like it too but
yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're talking about the cocktail aren't you
I love sex on the beach
that's a it's a cocktail
yeah yeah it is yeah you want to see what it looks like
I'll show you it actually looks really nice
why
because you'd said cocktail
oh god
it's like it's that meme of mr incredible becoming uncanny
Luca asking like hey what's a cocktail and expecting mister to send a picture of a drink
and then mister sends a picture of black and white
all right
vc that's what uh sex on the beach looks like
why is it called sex on the beach
because it looks like a beach
okay but why why the fornication where's the taste like sex
it's also got a cherry
yeah so if it's so so you can see you can park you can pop it you can pop the cherry right
I hate it here
oh like
oh I
is there a saying
it is yeah
i see
it's pretty uh
it's it's a more it's a more kind of kind of mr Vox type con context
uh but if if it was like you and i were playing chess for the first time like I introduced you to chess I'd be popping your chest cherry you know
uh
okay
it's like
there's so many ways to phrase that differently box why did you have to go with that
i think
honestly I think we should just scroll through and see the ones that like we think are interesting
yeah let's just test group
bless you
that's good to see
the toilet if it goes over
yeah
anything but over we're gonna have a problem
it's like it's like when they when they orient the toilet paper so the toy pepper the toilet paper like beats from the the other side
what I don't know these questions
what do you mean hold on I have a picture that perfectly some sums it up
okay
like like when you pull it off
no no no no I got you
i I the left is under the right is over
oh wait
you guys use though
dude I just put i put mine on the door handle
why door handles
i can completely understand just not wanting to use the toilet paper holder
and just kind of leaving it like maybe on the like on the the top of the toilet or maybe like nearby
the door handle just seems like a weirdly sort of like why would you bother
yeah it's like a little effort
the door is next to the the but then when you try and pull it off you're just going to yank it down and then it the door opens right
no but it's not always there I mean when I'm shitting
wait wait wait so when do you shit you pick up the toilet roll and put it on the thing
yes because then it's next to me
why do you bother
why not just put it on the thing and leave it there like another thing
i don't have a thing so I either put it like on the floor on the bathtub or i put it on the door you know
the door
hit the door
yeah you know how much unnecessary effort you're putting into this
while you guys do this in the uh the bathroom right
obviously you're cooking sausage or bacon which one which one which one huh
bacon is better than sausages I think
high five mister
is this like breakfast sausages
it's all about sausage barbecue sausages
barbecue sausages type of sausage Luca
huh
is that
there's only one type what it's not
that's only one type of sausage
what
oh my gosh it's like the only one type of nut thing all over again
i like uh
it's always good tumbling sausages
they're pretty anyway uh apartment or house
house
what the
that's a good question um
it's a good question um
for me I like houses but I'm also I'm drawn mo I think I'm drawn to apartments
because you can have them in a very central area
you know what I mean
like yeah like maybe in the mid like if you wanted to go really really central like the middle of a city
you're not going to find a house
like if you haven't if you haven't enough if i want to live
i feel like I'm
i don't know I can't be loud yeah
exactly I can't scream
i prefer a house yeah
there are solutions I mean look at me
I'm still in an apartment
I'm not gonna buy a sound booth
or or if they build the apartments well enough to the point where the sounds won't become an issue
that's best case
yeah that's also true
i feel like I'm more of an apartment person although I do like to be loud so then like there is like us i would have to try and fix that oh
also if you have a house you need anything that will block me off
it's when it's when someone like stop like
for example if if you're in a an apartment
you're being loud
they just stomp on top of you
yes yes yes that makes sense
oh yeah it's gross I mean I want to move
i hate him
like late night
that actually happened during our pro pound collab
really
yeah I got a stomp on me from my annoying neighbor upstairs
and I was like you you little it is it is a holiday you know damn well that people are off work
I'm allowed to be allowed around like 10 or whatever
like piss off
yeah I wish I could scream at like 3 a.m
yeah that's insane
adoring ever since I got the booth thing
i can be loud at any hour I want and not have a single worry
yeah since I stream in like under the living room
like for example when food's ready or something like that they call me by stomping
it is the most annoying thing ever
like just call me or something dude just message me why do you need to stomp
come down and knock on my door like a normal human being be like
yeah I don't blame you that would be like um it's like when people want to get my attention and they just whistle at me
that's like poking me in the eye
like I'm not a dog no offense mister
yeah it uh
he just lit him feeling his legs
it's the same feeling as the alarm
like that
no like stomping uh
while I'm like streaming or something same feeling as when you get woken up by your alarm
oh I know I know what you mean like
the the the default alarm noise that everybody grows to despise
do you have like my guys when you hear it you get kind of freaked out
yeah
when I hear that one it makes my heart beat
yeah yeah yeah it gives me like cold skin I hate that
there's this one uh alarms town I used to set
it's like uh it's like one of those alarms that you sometimes hear in movies
when there's like an like a alert alert
that was the one I said it as and then like sometimes in like movies they would play like the exact same sound and
and then I would like literally like be like oh I can't watch this anymore this is pain this is pain
yeah it's triggering my my past traumas like
uh it's so bad
it's only bad for that one because like that's around when like i had to wake up in the morning every morning for like school and stuff
yuck
i had to change my alarm sound so like I don't get that anymore
so bad
i used to have this one alarm clock that i used to joke was like forged in the fires of hell
because it was pitch black plastic that looked like it'd been melted slightly from heat or something
and the digits on it was like pure red that just glowed in the dark like a set of devilish eyes
and when you would like set that and then went off
i kid you not it was loud as hell and the like alarm tone was just a shrieking
it did not like it woke up the entire house but one thing that it was good at it was getting you off
because it would not stop unless you walked up and turned it off and I had it at the opposite side of my room
so at that point I might as well go get up
never like at that point
your your sleep is just going to be made awful by that kind of thing
like earlier on stream i had it I had one of my alarms went off
like I have an alarm clock that has two settings for it one of them went off on stream
that it's an alarm that like grab it's a light that gets brighter over about half an hour
and people are like what the fuck is
and then when it gets so half an hour before you wake up it starts getting brighter to simulate like the sun
and then you're like ah and when you finally wake up you're like ah
and then bird song starts playing you're like ah good morning everybody
anyone who gets woken up by phone vibration is just going to feel like you know
yeah yeah yeah yeah
you know do you have right on for your alarms
i don't think is that a setting
yeah
i put it on my legs
so it just like vibrates against your legs and that wakes you up
so mister just comes violently in the morning and that was what wakes up
and like Vox
from the leg if you put
i know like he didn't say that but he meant it
i oh that you're tall but you have must have very long legs in order to take these kinds of leaps in logic
i don't know I've never
mr and I are the same breed and I just kind of I just got to tell what he's getting at
like like when you had like an xbox or a ps4 or something like
I know what you mean right yeah yeah
and you just kind of like you know place it down
no
on your leg
oh
mister
on your balls mister
no no
i like putting the ps4 controller on my balls
no
i like the way it makes my balls feel
oh yeah
back to the topic of alarms
apparently if you like think hard enough like that you'll sleep this amount of time
and wake up at this time
you actually like don't need an alarm
yeah oh the internal clock
yeah yeah and then yeah
I've never used an alarm for like the past
whoa really
whoa you just wake up
yeah
oh
i don't ever use alarms for whenever i have to wake up for a collab
I'm impressed
yeah a lot of times like i know that I'm capable of doing that
but also I'm like uh you know I'll just rely on this alarm yeah
do you just kind of like sense it
yeah like like I work I i told myself i was going to wake up at 3 a.m today
because do I have to basically get ready for the collab
and I yeah i woke up literally 2 59
and my a lot like my backup alarm actually went off
all right do you guys ever like wake up just before your alarm
because that happens to me a lot
yeah yeah yeah
that's what happens when you yeah that's like that's like the human built-in clock yeah
i mean for me I'm I'm kind of more on the unlucky side of the spectrum
because whenever even though I do set alarms for things whenever I'm getting like a nap before like a stream or a collab or something
I wake up like sometimes two to three hours before it goes off
and then I just keep waking up and going back to sleep in like 20 minute increments
until the alarm finally happens
it's like my body is just like better better better wake up way in way in advance just in case
it's terrible
all I have to do is sleep for three hours and I'm I'm very energized I don't know why
but I don't think it's oh at all
I think three hours is like the the single sleep cycle right
I think um
it's like in three hour increments you sleep
and then like your your mind is like pretty refreshed after the three hours
cycle or something
yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're like mine your brains yeah when you sleep like your brain sorts out all like your your memories and stuff so if you
and the cycle ends in like three hours or three hours there's two cycles oh 90 minutes per cycle yeah okay
i never tried basically food
three hours only though I try to go for at least six
oh yeah yeah six hours is is is a good amount
like I i I feel like my ideal amount of sleep is about five hours but it catches up to me
you know like I'm always really awake if I sleep five hours but then two or three days of that and I'm like
yeah
i feel like no matter what I sleep oh my god the nerd
i feel like for me no matter how much i sleep
i will get tired during the day to the point where I'm going to want to take a nap regardless of what I'm doing
it's honestly kind of frustrating
but naps naps are so nice though
they are
i need my nine hours
before we debuted i would actually nap every single day
really
but uh
oh
and then a friend of mine said oh that's very bad you should never do that
nine hours is fine what's wrong with nine hours
they they're just they're just haters
the haters
yeah
i know this is really good what
i i nap I i napped earlier today
i can't understand how people nap because I feel more tired after I nap
i don't know
how long you now
yeah
me too but also I feel like I nap when like I'm already having a real
like if I'm having a day off a nap is fucking beautiful
do you know what the the right solution is for a day off when you want to just relax as hard as you can
what's your favorite youtube
so here's how it works it's it's a process right
your side of the your side like your desk you're just doing whatever you want you're like okay
i need to decompress so you go and you get an alcoholic drink of your choice
me right now I have a beer for me it's a beer that's my choice
you drink a beer and you watch a comfort youtuber you just kind of lie back and you're like yeah this is that
and then make sure that your bed is ready
and when it's ready you go and you have a hot shower
a shower that's like fucking just like like oh you're like really fucking hot shower
and then once that's all done
you just come back dry yourself off and collapse into bed and you will have the nicest nap
and then when you wake up when you wake up two or three hours later
order kfc
um
what can you order what can you order
some reason these guys
they have like 10 delivery every single time it's
i never buy from them
wait let me add something on to that
it's even better if your bed is like freshly made and all the like the bed sheets are like nice and cool
yeah you're right
wait do you ever just like take a shower and lie down on the floor
on the floor what
i don't like lying down on my sleeve because it's hard
yeah you just like turn it up all the way like no cold water at all and you just like lie down
what yeah wait
kind of get what you mean I mean my showers are not even like it's like a little circle
so I can't really do that but I'll sit on the floor sometimes and just kind of meditate
oh
oh just like sit down at the bathtub like under the running water
yeah raymond raymond understands
yeah
yeah I pass out there a lot well
it's nice it's therapeutic you know
it's a waste of water but it's therapeutic
yeah yeah you know when you're going to shower
did your showers ever used to like be hot and then it would just go cold randomly and then back to hot again
showers that have done that but like that's always been like when I'm staying at some other place
oh yeah that's usually when someone turns the scene right
that was it or yeah
turns the sync on flushes
little girl
yeah yeah
that's how their plumbing works right because it's all connected
that was one of the questions showers or baths
that's a good question like
it's a difficult one because where I'm living right now i don't have a bath I've only got a shower
I'd really like to go somewhere with a bath because I can't imagine like because baths are just so relaxing
i like showers I really like showers
the thing about baths for me is like like like uh filling up like the tub must be like convenient
the places I've been usually it was kind of a hassle like you had to go the extra mile in order to prepare anything
so like uh usually if you have like the bathtub in the shower like combined so it's like super easy and super convenient
then I would be having baths all the time but unfortunately I've never been that
fortunate to have anything like that at any place I've stayed
what if what if you're taking a bath and and you
such a heavy sleeper you tried you tried
to drown
i tried like sleeping
oh this did not work
um
when your head like goes down into the water you wake up immediately
yeah yeah
that's it's one of the reasons why they say it's impossible to like you know choke yourself to death
because like the instant you the water like before you die you'll pass out
and then your hands will fall off your neck and you'll wake up you know
Luca I think it's more of like if if you're asleep in bed right
and if somebody somebody just splashes water at your face wouldn't you wake up
yeah yeah but this is a bath though once you fall in
well well yeah yeah so i think it's like it's crazy
a bathtub is not 10 feet deep dude it's like fucking up to you
what type of bathtub are you talking about
you're not going to fucking drown in it dude it's not that deep
yeah like if it but if it ever happens think about it
your head's slowly falling into the water your mouth is in and and you start to uh
you wake up and you're like oh yeah you inhale it the water
yeah
i think I think I wouldn't panic though
I'll just be like oh okay I was asleep
and even if you were to like take a like to like get some water in your nose or whatever
the only thing that will happen is that like you'll recoil cough and get up like that's just going to be your instinct
and you'll be in you'll be in discomfort for a while but you'll be fine
the only way you're drowning in a drowning in the bathtub is if somebody else is the one doing the drowning
oh
i feel like
yeah that would suck from horror movies
i put my head down in the bathtub to wash my hair and I'm it's like underwater
I'm like oh my god there could be something like above me right now looking at me and I can't even know
no I relate to you there's have you guys seen on perfectly cut charts which is that two other accounts that I mentioned on stream all the time
there's a video of this dude who's like me trying to catch the ghost in my shower lacking
it's a guy in the bathroom just kind of like hanging out like not paying attention
he turns around and just punches the fuck out of his shower curtains so hard he just falls
but did you know if if you actually splash water in someone's face while they're sleeping
and they have like a whole like a whole five-hour drowning scene in their in their dreams
and they finally wake up it works
can I do that to someone
oh my god that's just this is how it is
i don't believe that so I want someone to do it yeah I do that's you
I wanna see
i wanna I wanna experience if that's the case
because like in your dreams it it takes it feels a lot longer
than it is oh yeah it does yeah like seven seconds could be like five hours
didn't they do that in inception
oh that's their whole thing right like you go into a dream and then it's longer
i never watch that movie
it's probably like a whole drowning like shipwreck scene and then like five hours and they finally wake up and like
water on me
fun fact about that movie I believe that at some occasion when it was being broadcast on japanese television
they actually added like a little thing in the top corner of the screen to like tell the viewers what the dream level they were at at any given time
if they thought it would be too confusing otherwise
oh
yeah like what is this baby o'clock you haven't watched inception if you don't if you don't forget what the top level of the dream is
you know you're just there and you think like oh yeah they're in the facility right now and then they go back and they're on the plane and you're like
you know like that's just what it's like
i remember watching the film but also i was like not awake because
i was watching it baby driver
yeah was so fucking good such a good fucking film
baby driver was dank
you haven't seen a tv filmed and like edited to the beat of songs
so like every gun every like door closed is like to the beat of the background music
it's really good
there's like there's an arms deal gone wrong where people shoot each other to this to the tune of I shit you not the tune of tequila
right yeah like guns going off like
like from the very beginning where it's like where he's just in there he's in the car waiting because the main character is a getaway driver
and all the people are in like robbing a bank and he's in this song and he's like what's up ladies and gentlemen I'm here to tell you about
the fabulous most groovy
bale bottoms oh my god I love it so
I want to watch the film again now
it's really rewatchable honestly yeah it is
that's the thing I love movies like that that you can get so much out of repeated watches
and he just says it's over leon
i just um how to train your dragon pawn
movie
it looks cute though I don't know
it's literally my favorite movie of all time oh my god Luca I love you
but it's still good
oh I've only seen the first one that
that's that's my favorite
even like you guys are talking about such good movies even onigiri is getting excited
and I don't know a more sarcastic and upset person
did I have dragons actually really good though
the the little mini series they had
oh I never saw that unfortunately
was it even about because I've never heard I've heard of it but I've never really looked into it
you ever seen like e.t or like any other movie but they're like hiding the pet from the parents or whatever
kind of like that but it's like that but it's a dragon yeah
the main character is like this is birth yeah and and like the vik yeah the vikings they kill the dragons so that's why he's hiding them
it's been a while since I've watched the second one's pretty good too
i will drag all of you along for a watch party I don't care I'm making popcorn
let's go
I've done I've done this let's watch along now
we need to do a Luxiem collab watch along you know
yeah
what are we watching
um
who killed captain alex
oh my god
i don't know that one roses are red violets are blue
dinosaurs
group watch the lorax
I'm sorry I'm going to be thinking about roses already violets are blue and dinosaurs
okay okay I got a question
either watercolor pepsi or cook
coke every day
immediately my fault Luca but then i drunk too much pepsi and now I can taste the difference
pepsi
coke is better by far coke is better
i will like I don't know I'm partial to coke they do taste different though
but the thing is the thing is i don't even think I
oh there's a coach right there I'll grab it
yeah same same
everyone ignore the fact
that my clothing has the same color scheme as a bottle of coke
i think coke is so much better than pepsi
because pepsi is I don't know how because coke probably has more sugar in it but pepsi feels too sugary
you know what I mean it is pepsi is way sweeter
pepsi sweeter even though coke has more actual sugar in it
there might be some regional differences between
that I i think that's very true because my coke is
definitely sweeter than my pepsi
really
you know the the clerk recipe is actually one of the most highly secure secured and protected uh things in the world
really oh yeah like a big fault
was it there's only two people who know it at a time
yes
it's kind of crazy
what's the sequence in a video game
what's the secret recipe to produce Luxiem
of the intro to the powerpuff girls
cringe paul
all of our ingredients is already on the table
oh a cat my hat a teapot uh
plushie
augustus
is he alive or is it plushy
you know you gotta figure it out he gets
bigger in my stream every single day it
doesn't move that life
okay and then a piece of shit
yeah
that's how you make money here it is
they become luxia
like sampling of the almond break throughout that entire show whatever any action is happening
it's so much better than in johnny tess with the whip crack
i never watch much of johnny tests about wow what is my inflection today johnny has
um
so like I don't know what the whip crack uh meme is that I see reference the line
I've I've never watched an episode of joining tests but I've seen clips where the whip crack sound effects plays at full volume like three times like five or six times in a minute
and it's just like wait what's going on
hey I'm doing okay
and it's it's scary
um you have to look this up
crack counter johnny test
that's terrifying one episode
wait one episode and it's one minute long
what
that's pretty long because there's just a sound effect
it's a sound effect that's like maybe half a third of a second
wait I'm going to use the russian real quick
you know what cartoon that slapped danny phantom
I never got to watch it but he was hot
anyways
but yeah like that that show was like so cool
and i it's a shame it lasted as short as it was
danny phantom I never watched it
oh my god like if you ever get the chance to like like find it on like a blu-ray collection or anything or if it's on a streaming service I don't know
I highly recommend it it's so much fun
oh it's more of a timmy turner
it's I believe it's the same creator
oh no right yeah
yeah
timmy and his something
did he say that
he did
where
let's take a dump
with his voice
i did not hear it at all
no no I get you
I've had so many
oh there's a japanese comment saying that your singing voice is a very lovely and wonderful box
really
yes
i I've never pranked as much as a singer I'd love this thing but I don't think I'd be very good at it
I'm not sure who you are but thank you very very much
that's incredibly sweet of you I'd love to learn how to sing but i don't think I'm very good at it
ah I also want to learn
it's been like something like I'm gonna drag all y'all y'all along and sing some stuff
it'll be fun it'll be great
saying that you would like sit there and listen while I sing
you know
yeah I can I can direct you guys like that's no problem at all no not at all
and they like kind of voice cracking stuff you're like
no i literally showed you my my outtakes
everybody singing well and then like
there are places where my voice cracks as well and it goes really really raspy
and you'll hear me absolutely flub everything underneath the sun tomorrow during the karaoke stream so don't you worry
I'm really nervous about that by the way
i like karaoke
nice
character
i kind of want to cover the second intro to death note
like I haven't watched that show in ages
i listened to it recently and I was like
yeah
like
yeah I'm not on the screen I'm I'm the poop
wait wait let me shoot let me get let me let me get you back in the action hold on
what's up okay that's how it's so good
shoot oh my hair's getting away
your fingers keep touching Luca's chin
yo it look it looks like you're giving him a little scratchy
yeah yeah hello kitty of that please
left
oh my god
she she's pogon based
let's see
like you're off the team
no
i like here
no no it's okay
i like you here too I like you hey
hold me kiss
I'm out of my drink
go get some drank boy
homie homies
just having a moment here
I'm looking spinning
we like to have moments here we like that fun
people like have fun here that's my favorite thing
like when something fucking mild happens we're like yeah we like to have fun here
we are taking a monochrome amount of that's what we'll tomfoolery
here out here
guys would you pick comedy or horror
for uh for me for
for what for what
in general like if you're watching something
watching something uh
comedy or horror
horror I i enjoy comedy but I feel like you can get that from a lot of places
like you laugh when you have friends you laugh when you watch most most films have jokes right
but i mean the ideal is a horror comedy but for which reason you should watch the lighthouse
but um for me I think horror sticks with me the most and it makes me like it kind of I don't know like artistically I find horror more inspiring
but I do love a good comedy
you know I don't know if this is based or not if this is like a base take but like
i think bad horror movies are still scary whereas bad comedy movies I'm not funny
yeah the thing is that is fucking so true
that is so true
like the thing about like when a horror movie is still kind of crap
if you're able able to be scared of it then there's still like something there for you to enjoy or like the experience that you're in it for
when a comedy movie fails at comedy it's nothing but pain
the word is joyless
right yeah joyless joy emoji
joy emoji flat face
like that that that's it
an unfunny comedy is bad
but an unscary horror movie is still like funny you know what I mean
sometimes unintentionally but still like
i feel like i can never not enjoy a horror movie
you know
there's actually one horror movie that i like I never walked away from a horror movie thinking like that was genuinely like bad
with the exception of one movie
am I allowed to say that
I mean I mean my entire personality is shitting on the lorax
I'm pretty sure you're allowed to like pick a least favorite film
there was this really obscure horror movie that for whatever reason like on imdb it was rated like fairly high
so I decided to give it a shot it was called recovery
and the whole movie was about somebody losing their phone and then turning it on recovery mode in order to find it
and it leads them to this abandoned house where some crazy people live
and it's i don't know why it's just really not great
um
and I just like walked away from it was like really
how how am I gonna watch tick tocks yeah
and check my my my my twitter
you guys can be willy's wonderland
it's like a nicholas the flat movie yeah
no but with nicolas cage as the stuff the trailer for that made me actually want to commit something
like the fact that the fact that they literally say they're not he's not locked in there with them
they're locked in there with him it was yeah oh it's so gross
I want the real snap movie to come out
oh yeah but like that has been in production for how long now
from from my understanding of it is that like um apparently according to the producer like jason blum blumhouse
like blumhouse makes so many horror movies like a lot of a lot of really good horror movies and some bad ones but whatever
they've said that like the fnaf movie is their highest priority and the main thing is finding a script that scott corton likes
and a lot of the time they'll present him with a script and he'll just be like now
um which I both admire and I don't because it's like yeah the movie is not gonna get made
but also it means that he loves his franchise enough that he has the integrity to be like this is not good no
um
i just I wanna I wanna I wanna see i wanna see something like springtrap in that movie
because his I think that's one of like the most violent villain deaths like possible you know
like an animatronic suit closing on somebody
holy shit that's grim as hell you know
and like the way the way it's depicted in like fan culture as well
I wanna i wanna see that shit that that'd make for a great movie
the games I don't like do they actually depict it in the game or is it merely impossible
it's it's imp it's it kind of implied so like at the end of an f3
um it's like the ghosts of the children that william afton killed all like kind of corner him in a room and he's like no no
and he hides in the the springlock suit that he used to kill all of the kids
and the thing about a springlock suit is that is that it's like an animatronic that you can kind of wind a crank
and then the animatronic circuits sort of open up and you can get inside and use it like a costume
um and so it's both but if the spring locks fail it just snaps shut and kind of just crushes you inside
and he jumps inside it hoping that he can like scare off the ghosts of these kids that he's killed
but because the building is so old the the ceiling leaks the joints get um get wet
and suddenly the whole thing just kind of collapses on him
and it's like all it is is him getting in the suit and laughing for a bit
and suddenly it's like and like there's this weird bit crushed sound effect and all this blood starts pouring everywhere
and it's like there's this one audio of someone having like voice acted it
and it's like him laughing and then suddenly you hear this like like and he goes like ah and like the screaming is so real
it's really really fucking violent
and like if they wanted to make a horror movie they need to put that shit in there because it's so it's so scary
like the idea of being inside a suit that just closes on you and then that that that's it
you know like it's it's fucking horrifying but I don't know
again we're back here with the Vox problem of everything coming back to five nights at freddy's
there is a enough
jesse have you solved the five threats
actually mr white I do believe I have back in 1963 william halfton created fredbear's family diner
no that's actually a question in there
oh okay uh nuts or no nuts
no nuts I'm not a fan
really yeah
it depends like again
um not from the nut tree
in chocolate fuck no I don't like nutty chocolate but
yeah no I don't like hazelnut chocolate i don't like nutella I prefer chocolate spread just regular chocolate spread I'm sorry
no good
but stir-fry
cashews and stir-fry yes please
yes please
unbased chocolate
i think it's like a thing back home that we had called the
toffee fae or whatever does anybody know what that is toffee is that how you say it called well coffee fee
see everyone chad's calling me based right
like like like like like nutty chocolate I'm not a fan of
but like come on cashews and stir-fry you can't really say no to that come on
some people are typing banned toffifee or however you pronounce it
that has like nuts in it
and for whatever reason that works for me like that that's the only time I'll have like nuts with anything
he doesn't have a good nut
pistachio is good
i like pistachios
wait pistachio and nut too
yeah yeah green type of knot
pistachios and not cashews or not
um we had this exact same conversation me or somebody else
well I played uno
Luca Luca was like
what what do you mean there's so much why are there so many nuts I i only thought there were peanuts
yeah I only eat peanuts though
i mean
they look the same but I thought they would just hold that and process like differently
that's how oh like all peanuts were like all right
what the heck happened Lucas sounded like he just got shot
what yeah i like mario when he dies
i was waving my recorder around and it hit my knee again
oh my god
that's my absolute favorite thing about Luxiem
is the fact that like the detective like the presid that the the arm of the law is the most corrupt and like unsafe member of the group
and then the member of the mafia who's supposed to have committed multiple crimes is just a pure beacon of light
that's not true
oh go go on
i jump
my profession a little bit too high to be right perfect
when have you ever
i only do curses I don't want to hurt oh
shoot cursed me would curse me with um curse me with um horny for Ike please
can't cast a spell twice
you know like I don't trust my trust my sorcery 100 though what if it goes wrong right
if it goes wrong maybe I'll just be horny for Ike in like a hateful way
you know and then we'll have great hate sex it'll be great
oh
that theme bomb on battlefield it's so good
um
yeah I don't think there's any game more nostalgic than mario 64.
i know I played it
oh how are you doing
it's like do you like platformers do you like platforms it's kind of old though
it's old but like okay okay mr mister do you like platformers
um i can't say I've really played many to be
64 was the first 3d platformer that was like good
it also introduced the concept of a camera that because it was the first game to use the term
like it's such a revolutionary game
playing the original like because I was honestly introduced to it through the ds version which is really different from the nintendo 64 version
the nintendo 64 version feels like you're just stepping into a dream
it's so old but it's so revolutionary at the same time
you know in the same way it mario 64 did for video games what 2001 a space odyssey did for films
you know what I mean like it's so wacky and new but also so old
but all in a way that it doesn't feel that old because the controls and the graphics still feel enjoyable today
in the same way that the camera work and the story of 2001 holds up in film today like it's it's weird
but like dude like mario 64 is a is an enigma
you've you have to play it it's beautiful
I've never
I've no I don't play that I've only seen um what's his name mischief like speed on the game
oh yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
i remember do you guys seen that clip of him trying to get the backwards long jump to get into the the top oh yeah yeah yeah
he can't get it and then emiru gets it first right he's like
backwards long jumps
mario backwards long jumps through your wall to wish you a merry christmas
it is sat there halfway through a bottle of wine alone feeling unloved on christmas and then you hear
yeah yeah yeah yeah
all of a sudden christmas is saved
the all blj the backwoods long jump
do you all know the trick in uh in the in this game that you could do a backwards long jump in school
I can't hear you
huge stuff that's oh
shoo
do you know that you could skip a huge section in this game by doing a backwards long jam
but before we elaborate further
we need to talk about parallel universes
yeah on the undertale stairs at the beginning in the ruins you could do a backwards long jump and skip the whole cutscene
was anyone else like really really unnerved by that part
like when you're good
like my first time playing I thought it would turn into a horror game I was really scared
oh me too
wait what part when you go down um
yeah it really freaks me out
there's this one horror tale fan game like an au of undertale called horror tale
where like that exact kind of shit happens and it's like oh
dang
if any if any fandom did it did alternate universes right it was undertale
holy shit
oh it's like it's been having problems with her
I heard a lot about like the au stuff when it came to that but I never really explored into it
hmm it's crazy it's crazy there's so much depth to it
oh
what the heck is luke doing he's gonna
let me set the server location
I'll set it to
being a little saucy
I'm going to set the I'm going to set the server location it might it might disconnect a bit
oh my god
hello hello
oh hello
i changed the location maybe it's better
hopefully
hold on guys I really have to take a piss I'm gonna be back in two minutes
I'll get out
yeah
I'm
as long as Luca doesn't have issues I think it's okay
i don't know why it's been doing that recently
it's never done that before
do you have like the in the settings do you have the what do you call it
enable quality of service hype packet priority on
where is that
in high chat voice and video
enable
quality of service just mid stream tech support
riveting
enable you're running this is what happens my face put the right remote
quality of service
i don't see anything here
in voice and video there's scroll down
is it
right is it is it on
it's on now
oh okay maybe I'm really tempted to crack into another drink and just like um it's non-carbonated by the way
because I'm sticking to that and just getting some cheese doodle sound I'm really craving a snack
oh
snook
snuck
I'm not really hungry
right that fun chat
I'm super hungry you don't have to be hungry to snacks do you sue well
I'm just vibing though
am I the only one that sometimes just like not because I'm hungry like I eat things just because I want something to do oh
yes that happens a lot that's actually how most people um like start putting on weight
because they are like normal wow mister
okay sure
I'm saying in general in general
oops ouch
dang
bruh
that happens quite a bit to me
I feel like I should just hang a sign into my fridge
so whenever I open it it's just a sign that hangs there says you're not hungry you're bored shut the damn door
honestly like I've seen a picture of that
ever since we debuted like i haven't this is not bad at all like I'm eating enough obviously
but I'm not eating as much
no
uh-huh yeah
I can kind of relate to that I don't like eat as much either
like I feel like the most I do is like sleep
I've been sleeping a lot more
really
I've been sleeping less
I've also been sleeping less I went to sleep at 7 00 am the other day
i sleep whenever
it's like I've been sleeping more but in shorter like increments
because for whatever reason I'm not I don't fall I fall into deep sleep as uh as much as I used to
and as a result I've been having a lot more dreams which unfortunately when it comes to me isn't is usually a bad thing
because my dreams are oh
my eating stuff is not bad at all like I'm eating enough I'm sleeping enough just not as much
as uh
it was before debut
um I kind of get what I mean whenever for me like
i don't know before i got here
i was just sort of like living to do stuff
and then when you start streaming and when you have like this schedule and when you want to do gorilla streams you want to do all this stuff
for me I will wake up to do a stream and then when I'm not streaming and i have one in the evening
my body will be like all right you need to rest go back to sleep for like three hours and then stream
and so for me it's like if I'm awake I'm streaming if I'm not streaming it's like yo go to sleep
yeah
like I mean the reason why I don't eat like a lot anymore is uh because your streams usually go for a long time
and if if I eat before that I'm not really burning that off
so that's right
yeah that's why
um also chat I want to say
um every member of loxiam their stream labs donation link is in the description
so if you want to send a question or a link to anyone in the chat please do consult the description
because they're all here on their own time so please be supportive just letting you guys know thank you
thank you
i just remember by the way Vox like during that whole um
are you seriously watching youtubers by yourself like
what prompted you to do that motorboating sound like the first time i heard it it absolutely shattered me like i was cry laughing
I don't remember what happened
I think it's like before because I tried to I tried I tried being like
like but whenever I did it and you enjoyed it my voice would break and it just kind of wouldn't work
so I was just like
and then like that that right there is like the majority of what I can do so right as my voice started to like her i would go like
and then suddenly like that would just kind of carry me ahead
you know what I mean like it's the way that you did it because like there was like a note underneath it so like it had like like underneath it
like moving back and forth like it absolutely killed me
like it was so bad like like it killed me on my first view and because it was on twitter it started looping
so it was like mercilessly just beating and kicking me while I was down
it's like I think it's more of a simpsons motorboat where he's like yeah
like nothing quite comes close to it it's like that lightning in a bottle on the one that ended up in the final cut it's so good
why
because you were like oh I was crying laughing
oh don't you mean joy emoji
oh my god crying who did this lmao
thing I am ulama fouling only foul
I'm fucking emoji
i never thought I would say lima foul but like absolutely saying it so many times it's just
I'm lumpfelling
how's it going
that's one thing that's changed in my month of streaming
i think I've got more organized as time's gone on
i think when we were playing our final scenes yesterday I was uh getting chased by rimu
and I was just yelling that at her
like ruffle ruffle ruffle
psychological warfare with Luca
i sleep
i spit people have been asking me to spit
like after my after my confessions stream I did a voice note because I was like these fuck are gonna like this
i just I just went to my bathroom and i was like hey and I just spat in the sink
and people like no my lord are you okay like they were genuinely concerned for me I was mad
I think I spat so hard they thought like was that him just like smacking something which is he's falling over did he hurt somebody
I was like no
i spat in the sink are you guys not horny already
jesus I thought this was like wanted
did you spit out a teeth did you lose a teeth
no it was just a load of spit i was like oh two
two
eight two put two
me too mister right yeah yeah
what what i guess
after all the times I've spat in your mouth mister you really didn't enjoy it
no it scarred me for life
ah
sorry uh
sorry about it
I'll spit somewhere else say okay
you're a silly boy mister but you do make me laugh
spit jump
why why would you say spit
what even is that
false camp but spit plus champ
yeah a champion um no
no
there it is every luxian cola has to have one mister like that
this is the second one
is it what was the first one
I don't remember I don't everything start blurring together with you after a while
i remember in the proper night collab you said you were going to start twerking
in the minecraft collab you said spank me daddy
um
and then you snagged me
I did it was fantastic and you're like
have you seen the animation of that it's great
yeah I have it's really good yeah
oh my god I think I know what you're talking about
it's good
that's the worst part like
even though like some of our listeners or viewers i should say and like um take some of our most cursed moments
they make like amazing art with it art animation and whatnot
like like the creative and creativity on display is impeccable but my ears are hearing cursed things
wait it's you know it's such a contrast or like what's the cognitive dissonance
um yes
um you know Vox you said earlier like donate to the other guys
mm-hmm
i got a donation just now and I just want I kind of have to read this because I'm kind of scared
no boy
you angel full stop
you precious darling boy
you adorable thing I would die for you
I would kill in all capitals for you
she's a precious precious darling angel
you're adorable
you're a ray of light
summers sweet summer child frick good
vlogs
I'm not gonna lie
that sounds like okay it's interesting
like mister i think your fans and my fans are sort of on the same level of down bad but for different reasons
you know what I mean really
like yours you're from that it's like
oh my god
i want to take you into my house and i want to put you in a little house
I want to put you in a little kettle and just want to take care of you for the rest of your life
and then my channel
and then my channel like can you please make a sound like you're slapping me up like I've melted into a delicious chicken soup
no is that
now is that because that's just how they are or is it because of the confession streams you've done
because like if if mr were to have a confession stream I'm sure that would do
well
i
um
i mean maybe maybe it wouldn't do as well as the original kindred stream
but i think it would
and I think it would i think it would and it would be the same sort of thing
I mean people and people in mine are like I just
the best one that I remember was from was it akamatitis522
who was like I want to just smash my face into your titties and then just let you eat your chicken strips and drip buffalo sauce into my hair
um
i don't even know what to say to that
it's kind of fog
like part of me is puzzled like how does
like how how do you develop a dynamic like that with your viewers
like it it seems it it it's baffling to me it's puzzling
it's like a riddle I can't solve
I mean that was in my first week
I hadn't done more the first week I hadn't done much at all then
i had I like that it said like by the bonfire so I'd played dark souls 2 and eaten chicken
by the bonfire in dark souls 2 because i was hungry and we'd been streaming for like five and a half hours
so I got some chicken wings with some spicy buffalo sauce and I've been eating them
and they were like yo I want to thrust my head into your titties and just let you drink that buffalo sauce under my hair
and I was like while you were playing dark souls
I was playing dark souls 2 of all games dark souls 2 scholar of the first shit
something tells me that you don't have a very healthy relationship with that game
after the end of that endurance stream
like my my enjoyment ended when I killed that troll in the tutorial with my bare hands that was fun
and then after that it was just a long painful slog to the rest of it
i will say though that like that one tweet for you were just looking really like defeated and depressed
and it just said dark souls 2 made me laugh really hard
dark souls 2
dark souls
um yeah
i kind of want to play dark souls again honestly
which one dark souls 3
3 yeah
dark souls 3 is such a good game and to be honest I think it's the best entry point for the souls series because overall it's the least like jank
like you will die if you die it's your own fault I think in dark souls 1 and 2
there are so many times where you'll die and it'll be due to like weird hitboxes or bugs all that kind of stuff
dark holes 3 is very is vicious and hard but very fair
and I think as long as you treat it with as long as you really try
if you beat dark souls 3 you'll be ready for the rest of the series honestly
I'd say go dark souls 3 then try bloodborne then try securo
and then try just what whichever ones you want oh secure
securo is mechanically the hardest but also the most fair
the boss like the final boss of sakura is the hardest boss I think I've fought in any game
I i love secular i played recently too
sakura is a beautiful game beautiful game
I hate it after having failed my no death runs in it that many times
but I i still love it you know it's such a beautiful game
secure is nice
i really love how yeah
you can you can just clash the hardest boss I've ever beaten like
it's it's pretty obscure like and I don't know how much I can talk about because it is very spoiler heavy and the main reason to play the game that it hails from is because of the story
ah I said I i want to like go into detail about any gush about it but i don't want to spoil just say the name of the game I'm the boss
um the final boss of dragon guard three
I know exactly what you're talking about and chat missed it uh mr Ike is absolutely right
that boss it like it for me I i got it on my fourth try because like you know I'm I'm pretty good with rhythm
uh but I have heard of people like literally being on that boss for months until eventually giving up
uh it is that like if you are not like a person who is like very good with rhythm you're gonna have a really rough time
i I i I don't mean to change topic i just wanted to point this out quickly for a second
yeah go for it
the donation I read out
uh you know the one that was like I'm precious or whatever they just donated again
but oh they donated five hundred dollars
saying I'm crying I'm sobbing on the floor I didn't think you would read that la mao I adore you here's your birthday present
oh
thank you mr sugar mama
what oh my god
oh they donate to me like occasionally as well I'm glad you have a sugar mama you deserve it man
oh I just noticed that I got a few donations too
oh that's awesome oh my god you guys are giving up your time to be on the stream you deserve it
from zero and zero jdk shannary m peepee
one of my favorite clips is um someone asked me like
hey you know can I have some advice for like someone i really loved rejected me recently
and i gave them like it was like five minutes of me just being like you know it's going to be all right and all that kind of stuff
and then I just moved to the next donation so it was like yeah i promise you man it's gonna be completely okay all right
pee pee poo poo and I just
the transition
the i like that I like that very much
not not biased or anything
like Vox asked
to present one thing that represents myself and I i got this poop so
when you say that word and you replace the last letter with the letter d
i don't know why but it just tickles my fancy in just the right way it's so funny
shid
you don't know what you're saying you know what it is
okay maybe this was a bad idea abort abort abort
sure
still such a missed opportunity
favorite color to wear
yeah
mine's black
oh that's a nice yeah that means simple
uh
i like wearing white and gray
yeah me too white and gray white because it gets and doesn't get too hot in the summer
why
what color do I like
I mean I like yellow and white literally I i like it yellow and white
I'm partial to blue and white a lot i mean I like can you tell me
I'm a big fan of red and white to be honest I mean like guys just look at our designs yeah
yeah look at the orange
i hear that it's less than you're needing to wear blue
mr you and me we gotta go to like
i don't know I don't know in the uk like what kind of like good clothing stores we have
we gotta go get you a good orange shirt you know what I mean
primark
the mystery Vox primock collab
shopping
shopping collab
it's a it's a clothing store in the uk
that sells clothing that is relatively inexpensive
oh my god like kmart
yeah game whatever that is
yeah kmart
my little pokemon is that yeah we have kmart keep getting closed down because they go bankrupt
but kmart just kind of keeps persisting you know
it's eternal
the eternal came no no kmart's not dead in australia
they're pretty dead
kmart over here being like I am inevitable
it's so cool how they have like seven dollar shirts
dusty still arrives all the time
i think it's pretty wait when's the last time I've been to a kmart
they're still in the box there's still donations trickling in ever since you mentioned that
somebody just called me an internet funny man
resident funnyman Ike eveland
thank you safrodisiak and 104 for just giving me a donation
funny
they are coming in though
yeah it's it's really sweet
i gotta like gain a question we can do for each other
mm-hmm for each other like from like left to right you know how we are on Vox's screen
oh yeah yeah yeah like first impression of me I do my first impression of clarkson and like that
onwards like that's only fun that sounds fun
first impression oh so we're doing ikes first
yeah yeah I i you do your first impression of me
and then I do it of
yeah wait wait I'm I'm confused like so would i
uh I should go ahead shoot
why don't we all do our first impressions of like collectively
okay okay yeah yeah I think that's a good idea
yeah so we start with like
okay so mister you go first give me your best me
uh wait wait um wait I don't mean impression like this
is it it's it's impressions like when we first met each other
no no no no no I wanna hear missed as me
uh
well
when I first met you
no
not like my actual impression
yeah like like impersonate me
oh okay um
um
i can't do this
hi everyone welcome to the stream
it's not bad
and uh I I'm just gonna go like
oh
whoops okay there he goes
are you okay
oh no okay
okay now let's do what shu properly said
yes
first impression
first impression of you ike
i think
uh
i don't know you you have quite a friendly voice right so like
i think um
immediately I was like okay I think the other least intimidating to me to to message
so I think yeah
but I think our first message together was like really
really corporate
was it right it probably was
yeah
that was my first impression of you
reading first messages now too
oh god I don't know if we have to go that far
okay
for some reason when I first heard your voice I couldn't tell why but I thought you were from hawaii
oh yeah we had the whole conversation wait yeah I remember you saying that
i couldn't tell why but from the very beginning
i just I i don't know why but I felt like I just thought you were really cute
oh
i was like man whoever this guy is
i want to keep him safe
and that was right ordering order and people he's very kind of you
all right that's very that's that's very cute though
hell yeah
and Lucas wait am I next oh yeah
well
it's kind of the same as missed that like I i thought um Ike was actually going to be a very quiet type
but not really chat
i can I am live with his voices and i i can't wait for you guys to hear it
let's go
uh-huh
quiet to uh lion roar there you go
rxdc
rxdxdxd
my first impression
honestly
i think the only thing that was on my mind when i first
my first impression that just comes to mind is you're ordering pizza
oh yeah I did do that
pumpkin then we were like guys
I've just decided you're like what pizza did you order and then you said hawaiian pizza
and that's my no no
wait I didn't order oh no we asked
oh no no we were like did you order hawaiian pizza because we think you're from hawaii for some reason
and I i said no
and then okay that's my first impression though
yes I was the pizza dude
yeah okay my first impression of mista
i thought you were very like quiet and reserved
but then like when we started like speaking a little bit more like it properly in voice calls
i started to notice the the say sus
oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah
because like like every little opportunity to sneak in an innuendo like mister would jump on that in a heartbeat
and it like slowly it started to form like his his brand
so like I started seeing glimpses of his true power I guess
and then when I saw him like in action on stream I was just really impressed because oh my god you are such an entertainer
it was I was in awe it was inspiring to watch
thanks
see sauce
all right dad what do you got for me
see mister
at the very beginning I wasn't sure what to make of you
because the first thing that I knew about you was the fact that in slack
you set your status to I'm scared of social interaction and I was like man this guy's this guy's quirky
and but the the truth is
when I when I actually got around to knowing you I think that you're you're the kind of person who is closed off from the outside but fiery and exciting on the inside
and whenever we spoke you're active
you're funny you're exciting and I think
i don't I don't think I've ever met anyone quite like you
and I know I like to bully you but maybe it's because today's your birthday and I'm feeling quite emotional
but to be honest I think that you're a very special person
and if you are scared even if you are scared of social interaction
the social interactions you had with me were really quite something
so thank you mister I think you're really cool
mr was very quiet and like
yeah I i think the other guys can speak can back me up on that
and like the more I got to know him like i don't know I feel like I can send mr anything
you said
that was content
like uh yeah yeah like
at the beginning I i wouldn't think I'd be able to do that with you
yeah but uh
yeah like one day we were on the call
we were talking about thanos
and I just sent it to mister
like a whole picture of ben or snake
yeah
Luca has sent mystic
oh my gosh
Luca sent me there
there was a reason why we did that okay we were talking about it
yeah you're like have you seen that this uh the thanos discord image
and we look we all looked for it in google images and send it to each other
oh my god
uh no Ike was the only one who didn't know what the fantastic was
why would I know
i didn't know either
or I don't did i
i think I don't think I was I don't think I was there during the
i would have preferred to remain blissfully unaware but I think these guys didn't like me
i might have been there
like I i
i recognized the phrase
i think that's about it yeah
why is this a phrase like why is this no
oh no I i have some friends that say stuff like that
but anyways my first impression
i think so do y'all remember when uh we had that one meeting and the manager's son was like
now you're officially part of ninja sanji welcome
yeah I remember that and then that's when i first heard mr go
let's
yeah yeah like you know usually once when they say like welcome to this or like welcome to that
like usually i think your response is supposed to be like oh thank you I'm glad to be here
you know those kind of things but like literally what we did was like
let's go let's go boys yeah we got it yeah let's go baby let's go let's go
yeah that's literally
how we reacted we pogged
but yeah um so
um out of that I think i remember miss does let's go being like the most
i think it was the first one
yeah I think it was the first one
and i was like oh like yeah let's go baby
like I followed up and stuff but I think that's my first impression I was like oh yeah
this is how and kind of as a whole i was like oh yeah this is how loxim is going to be
logging says
yeah yeah exactly
exactly
all right I guess what next
huh oh shit all right
my first impression of you Vox
de monkey
i think my first impression of you when I heard you speak
I'm like I mean no offense but I was kind of scared of you
oh
why you were a little bit i don't know like it wasn't that just like oh like like a deep intimidating voice
it's just like you seemed so in control
like when I heard you speak I just knew that oh my god this is somebody that probably knows exactly what they're doing
like has a roadmap figured out for everything planned into every little minute to detail
and just I i just knew that like oh my god he's gonna be so successful successful and everybody's gonna like like fawn over him his looks his voice and everything
and just to some extent I was correct
but now you're to me at least not intimidating
you're like a big cuddly teddy bear you're just such a comfy person to be around
you're always gassing me and the others of Luxiem up
and like just the everybody in ian you're such a positive force that's just constantly present
you're gonna make me cry
i distinctly remember like when we were like I was being nervous like uh before we uh we were announced with debuts and everything
and you you said something I don't remember the exact topic but you said something
it's just king supporting kings don't even mention it
and i that just stuck with me
that's yeah that's it you know
you got you guys are all a load of kings
you've worked so hard to be here
of course
you posted cringe
well my first impression of vlogs was pretty similar to that
in a sense that he seemed like
and I don't mean this in a bad way for everyone
I just mean like he seemed like he knew the most about what what he was doing like leading the group in a way
um like in the cools like when we were doing like uh our meetings and stuff
it kind of felt like okay he's like like I can rely on him you know
like if he if he has like an opinion on something that we're we're doing like kind of like oh okay yeah
i I kind of agree
yeah like the dad of the group
um that was my first impression I was like
oh oh actually i wouldn't say I was scared of your voice
um but i was intrigued I guess
oh I was like i couldn't
oh you sneaky little devil
american
i had to like kind of message you
and then and then of course we were two brits and I was like brit's got to stick up yeah yeah
yeah because I really wasn't it was hard to discern like everyone's accents and i didn't want to ask to be like
I don't know I thought it might have been rude to ask for everyone
so I kind of just yeah
I'm really learning time
american
healthy yeehaw
yeah as for my case I i thought fox was gonna be well
still is like one of the mature ones of the group
uh when he's when he first started speaking actually
because yeah like uh like what mr said he he would actually lead the meetings sometimes
yeah like if if he had a question he would just go go and say it
and stuff like that and
that that's why he gave me that impression
but now this is very sassy very sunny
yeah he's uh he's very kind very very kind
and very supportive
thank you
my first impression
uh
i think the one thing that really stuck to me was like
when um after our first meeting like we didn't even we didn't have any like contact information of each other yet within the group
and then and then fox was like so when are we when are we able to contact each other
when are we getting our own group chat when are we whenever we chat and you know
like Vox was always the guy who asks like uh
oh no oh no I want to meet my gem mates you know
yeah yeah yeah like that was that was my first impression I was like oh oh yeah he's probably a friendly person you know uh wants to just know
i guess very socially active I guess is the way I'd imagine
was my first impression yes
man you guys are so sweet yeah what the fuck
I'm supposed to I'm supposed terrifying 400 year old demon from hell
and you're all like hey this I i like this guy and I'm like
don't worry about it it's just king supporting kings
thank you guys whenever whenever I have a tough week I know I couldn't rely on you guys so thank you
hog rivers
oh
thing yes that
um
i had a little bit of a hard time like like what's the word I'm looking for
like nailing down what kind of personality you had in the beginning
because I feel like along with mr you were also a little bit quiet in the beginning
but once we got started talking a bit
i could like see like I could feel the sort of like like really upbeat energy that you can't uh tend to have
like you told us about how you were really good at getting over it and we were like no way
and then he just went on stream and beat it in like no time at all right in front of us
and we were just kind of left speechless
and I also remember the first time you told us like about lucy
and I was just like there's no way
like like I was like okay you know what then like give him like show it off like like let's see what you got
and I was just blown away with your fluency in grill
yeah I i I did the bed with them I think
and yeah like it's like it still surprises me to this day like how blown away I was with that
and but like I didn't really get like like a firm like uh grasp on you as a whole
until like we started getting real close to debut and started talking a lot more
because that's when your like the whole
the era of pog started like really clicking with me because the occasional pogs that I caught never really stuck with me
but after a while I started realizing wait a second there's a pattern here
and now here we are and it's slowly starting to spread to the rest of the eg ends
is
yo like there's one time somebody uh somebody was posting like a clip of Luca translated but they didn't translate pog
oh owl
japanese japanese japanese pog japanese japanese japanese
subtitles
they just could add a translation note for it
like they don't even have the translation though it's just pog
oh no they just assume they just assume
it's universal
it is
oh god I appreciate that I like thank you thank you thank you
thank you
first impression of Luca
again I couldn't tell where everyone was from when we first started speaking
and you know the first ever times we all heard each other's voices I think
we weren't you know we were all kind of silent for most of the call
you know
so it was kind of hard to even tell much about each other until we got into the slack
and then I think that's when i
started getting in front yeah but like uh i think and I was intimidated by Luca actually
uh oh
and I messaged him on slack
and like because I messaged like everyone right like I at least tried to like kind of slide in a little bit
if it wasn't in a group chat then it was in dms
and i messaged Lucarin in slack like dms
and he like didn't reply for like quite a few hours
and I was like oh god does he hate me
but I think it's because it was time zone oh no
oh wait
like for something
in that case I i missed your message for like a whole three days
the first one
yeah I'm pretty sure you fell asleep
but
it stopped I stopped being intimidated when we actually started talking
um hey
the moment you added the sassy emote to a comeback oh god that thing
yeah
i was like okay this person is not intimidating at all
oh I remember that time when you
i didn't realize until like I think shu pointed it out
yeah and it took a screenshot
okay
it was genuinely hilarious
yeah
my my first impression of Luca to be honest I was like kind of terrified
because his i don't know why but Lucas way of communicating is so different from what I was used to
that something about the way that when we called he spoke I was like the hell is wrong with this guy
like i was really just i was really just confused I was like what's what the hell is going on
but then when we actually got around to streaming and he started showing that sense of humor to everybody I was like ah
i like I started really getting it and now that I see who Luca is and who he is to everybody like I really really get it
and honestly like at first i was like I've never I think the fact is I'd never spoken to someone with his sense of humor before
and now that I see how he acts on stream and how he's been acting since we've gotten to know each other better
he is one of the funniest people I know
like he comes up with such amazing in-jokes
he's so quick to come up with with with all of this shit
and like I i really really think that Luca is such like a comedy genius
and hanging out with him makes me feel
i don't know I don't know
i think I think that his sense of humor is such a unique thing
and at first i was scared of it because I didn't i didn't get it
i was like what the fuck is this guy trying to say
but like now that I've actually properly seen it I'm like okay okay
this guy knows what he's doing and he absolutely is like
he's in luxian because he knows what the fuck he's doing and I was like shit
i absolutely I don't even know how I act
i I i absolutely gotta like being quick with the comedy
because like do I need to remind you of the lookie incident
lookie less
yeah sorry I I've grown I've grown immune to it but like the way
the way Luca said it when it happened how casually like it was such a drive-by statement from him
and I wasn't prepared for it at all and it just took me out
well thank you fox
that's okay buddy
thank you
it's very sweet of you
i think my first impression is kind of more of like a like a what like uh what do you call it
it was kind of like I just I just ordered some food I'm gonna be right back
oh okay okay okay
yeah but okay what I what I thought it was kind of like an episodic memory right
so the first thing I thought of when i when uh when we were all just talking right
and we were like hey so well do I would you mind if I ask where y'all are from
I think Vox asked that
and then uh we we we are like oh I'm from here I'm from there
and then and then after i think I was the last one to answer that question
um but I think that was when I also heard Luca say oh I'm from australia
and I was like oh shoot he's australian
oh shoot
um
but then also at the same time I was like wait am I the only an a guy in the whole group
and then like that that worried me a little in like you know many ways
but like but like also I was like
whoa
kangaroos
I'm sorry like every time every time like you know this isn't really a first impression
but that's kind of like the things that I just think in my mind when those kind of things happen
so it kind of is a first impression but also not
um the first actual like impression of Luca as a person
not not his country
um is uh probably when uh we were in call that one time um
and then we started sharing like tick tocks with each other
yeah yeah
every tick tock Lucas ends contains at least like
like I'm trying to like wha what is that genre of tick tock
it's like surreal kind of like it's like it's like those tick tocks where like you don't know what's going on at all
but like at the end they just have like a zoom in of their face
like like a zoom in of like a giraffe's butt and it's like the funniest thing ever
but like the talk talk itself makes no sense but there's like some random funny image at the end
or like some random edit that makes it really funny
you know that kind of energy and I was like oh shoot this is the kind of vibes we're heading towards icsc
and then I think that's kind of like was uh what uh showcased like how eccentric is that the word
yeah because
yeah that's the that's the kind of kind of vibe that I i felt from from Luca
and also the and then and then um while we were calling also Luca has a really loud mouse wheel for some reason
oh yeah
you'll hear that like listen to that and it used to be so much worse
look like he would he would scroll through that and he'd be like what what's going on what what what are you saying keeps on scrolling on it
and then I was like i don't know it's not really like a clueless thing
but like it kind of like carries on to like other things
like um you know you know in the the friday the 13th collab
when when pomu and I was like looking at the sky
yeah
yeah we were like yo look at the nice guy look at the nice guy
and then you start looking at the nice sky
but we were actually not looking at the nice guy and we're just looking at butts
why oh the ass of the character
yeah but
that wasn't really my focus
yeah we were like whoa look at the nice guy whoa whoa
well would you look at the whoa whoa whoa look at whoa whoa oh my gosh
what are you looking at
like what do you mean what do you mean
we're just looking at a bus
but I think like something similar is like just still present throughout the time
but that was the first time I really saw those kind of moments from Luca yeah
do you guys remember that one time when we were like chilling in cold with Luca and then he just like shouting
and we were like like we went there when the full aussie came out
yeah yeah when the full aussie came out in his voice
and we thought he was just like doing an impression or something
and he was like oh no was my mic
i know exactly what has happened
so uh we were we were thinking of um the lines for the uh the trailer remember that
oh right right
i was I was playing new world at that time
and in new world you can actually uh like voice chat people
so this this uh this low-level dude had pvp on
so I turned on voice chat and actually started speaking in a really super thick australian accent shouted
i didn't know these guys could hear me
yeah
before you push to talk on you said
i thought I had push the talk on in slack but slack doesn't have push to talk
yeah yeah
and we were all like what what's that
i was like oh my god get the hell out of here
yeah it was like i don't know
like taking the piss but no like he was actually just shouting at someone
it was glorious that moment lives rent-free in my head
oh I mean I just talked about you being australia
but yeah
shoot
my first I think Shu took me the longest to like sort of nail down like what kind of like what kind of vibe you had
i don't know like there if there's a specific reason for that or if I was just really dense which you know is very possible because I'm not very bright
honestly I just feel like it's it's pretty unclear honestly
like like you know luke is pretty clear-cut
and mystis is like oh yeah
once you get a grasp on it it's like pretty cut and dry and like it's all there in front of you
like I had a hard time figuring figuring out like what kind of kind of energy you would exude
it became like more and more clear as time went on
like when when I saw that you were like gathering evidence dot zip and just just that name reference sort of started giving me an idea
and you were very open to using the saucy e mode so that was also a big clue
okay
and and then with your worksheet
with your lore video for debut I was like okay okay
yeah but prior to that I i just everything was sort of a blank slate for me
I wasn't entirely sure and like this really mean part of my brain was just like
hmm i wonder if he speaks that way to me because he doesn't like me
but like i know that wasn't that wasn't the case
but I it was just like a really how did i speak how did I speak
was it like that you didn't speak any particular way i was just over analyzing it like an idiot
oh
it's like before I had like under like understood you more as a person
I was just like reading way too deep into things and just coming to the worst possible conclusions like a dummy
but once like or more I got got more of a grasp on it
i was like okay okay I i get that this is what this dude is about
and you're a riot to be around it's always a lot of fun to see
you're always so like organized and know like how to figure stuff out
and like i don't know if you you guys are aware
but like shu is like the one that's like who has been pitching a lot of our like collab ideas and funny stuff
like that whole seriously watching the tubers by yourself thing was his idea like
I think you also suggested prop night which again
I think is like one of the highlights of my my time here in lexium that collab just it was so much fun
yeah
i had lots of plenty
argue
i uh I actually agree with Ike if like i can pinpoint um you right away
like how you your personality was um
and I think that's mainly because you do such a good job of like uh kind of adapting to whoever you're talking to
so like um you around like me only me would be different to you me and Vox
or you me and Luca would also be different or
yeah I think you're good at adapting to what whoever you're around you know
um
and so like i also didn't ex I didn't expect you to be so organized
like you're i think when you organize something like a collab it's really like
it's really hard to get us all to say like exactly what we want or need or think about a collab right
because we're all in different time areas or we all have something to do or busy with streams ourselves
but somehow when you do it like it always leads to a good result
i don't know how you do it
you just you
and I don't know how
so I'm very impressed by that
but yeah
when I first messaged you I was
i wasn't like i think I thought you were quite mysterious which is ironic considering
hey yo
the reason why I thought that you were quite mysterious is because we like immediately called like the guys we all called
but um you couldn't make it to the call the first time
so we got to know each other a little bit first and then we didn't get to know you just yet
so i was like
they're so mysterious what could they be possibly doing
like yeah
cool
pretty cool man
oh oh thanks thanks man
that would be pretty cool though
it would be pretty cool though
this box here
i am here I've had my game down I've been eating chicken and it's been real good
um
shu you scared me yes
because his wife
because we were having a call and slack it was me Ike Luca and mister
and we were just kind of hanging out we were shooting the what the fuck
and then Lucas's guys all right I'm uh I'm gonna go to bed
and then he just went to bed
i shit you not 10 seconds after he left you joined I was like
oh yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
who is this guy
like you had not joined us yet and I was like man I wonder when she's gonna join
the instant Luca is gone it was like you just stole his life energy and just were like
finally a moment to communicate
and it was just had to be he's like
to be honest it's like within 10 seconds
it literally was it literally was
and then like not fitting with the narrative I'm trying to spin about shu
but then ten seconds after shu left the call later on
Luca joined again and I was like yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
i remember
let's tell you the truth true
it's like i think I agree with all the other guys is that it was hard to put a pen on you
but the main thing is that like especially from the way you communicate and from your debut as well
I was like this guy is a leader he's uh he's like diaz guy you know
shu thinks of the collabs he helps with technology
he's he's he does so much to help Luxiem run as smoothly as it does
and believe me Luxiem doesn't need to run smoothly to run in a way that's funny
but if it needs to run smoothly shu is there and he's always coming up with all of these unique ideas
he's always doing all of this unique stuff to try and figure out like what he needs to do to make things work
and i I i think he's frankly incredible and to be honest like the way he looks overall
I think I might overall be kind of down bad for him the most I have to say
i mean look at this man's arms look at his hair look at his eyes
oh yeah we all didn't realize how buff she was at first yeah
I i think I might was the first one to point it out
like when I was when I saw the rest of you guys the first thing I said was what are those guns though
yeah I don't need sorcery with these
my first impression of Shu was actually is that
I i uh i thought she didn't like me
because I messed the Shu like oh it's finally nice to uh talk to you
and and like you didn't reply for two days I'm like oh god
yeah I didn't understand the the slack dm feature at first
yeah i don't know
and then once he finally uh it replied like because I always dm people in all caps most of the time
yeah
I think that's the case for everyone here
when I first like started talking to them in dms it was all caps
and like she replied with full caps also and I was like okay okay
come on like like
okay he's uh oh he's he's good he's good so far he's good so far
and so far
again like we didn't really get to talk to each other for like a while because i time zone differences
sometimes he would be asleep and I would be like awake
and all that
yeah but no like honestly I think out of all of us
like in terms of uh daily streaming like necessities
I think I think she's like one of the most uh reliable people
you can kind of have around and obviously like he he helps out with a lot of tech stuff
and which is very very kind of them
oh I almost forgot when I first heard your voice
like uh-huh i was like oh his voice is very anime
it's very anime
it was very cool like very cool oh this guy's a really like nice sounding like the way he pronounces words was it was really nice
oh
yeah like that's what I thought
oh thanks
nationals
and yeah like he he just talks like that and I was like oh that's pretty that's pretty cool
i talk
yeah that's mine
that was my first impression that's everyone
oh that's everyone
look how far we've come give it up for lexie
and we'll give it up for us guys holy shit
everyone's been so good
a bunch of good boys
pod gurs
how long have you been we've been live
for three hours now yeah
it's passed so quickly
it has it has
oh yeah is this a good place to
i think this is a good place to end
yeah i think we've been funny
we've been sappy we've been everything
but yeah um I think hang on
i think that would be a good place to end it for tonight
thank you guys for coming to the one year one month anniversary
one year what the fuck
one month is something different
but this is
i know we've been time traveling but this is ridiculous
um we've had one month
and I just want to say thank you guys so much for coming out and for wishing us well
thank you
one month anniversary thank you all so much
and we will see you all in the next stream that whichever one of us decide to do
so thank you so much for seeing yeah oh for one month
we'll see you all every two months three months four months who knows
you guys for everything
and we'll try to keep making me happy
goodbye everybody yeah thank you so much
you